Welcome to our training on the Manage Your Compliance Dashboard.
In this module, you'll learn how to view and respond to product compliance requests and how to submit
the required documentation.
You'll also learn how to appeal compliance requests.
It's important that products in the Amazon Store are safe for customers to use and that listings
are fair for all sellers.
Everyone who shops and sells in the Amazon Store must be able to trust that the products are held
to the highest standards.
It's also important that sellers can file and organize all the necessary information and documentation
to show that their products comply with Amazon's policies and government standards and regulations.
The Manage Your Compliance Dashboard is designed to make this process easier by allowing you to
organize, submit and track your compliance documentation in one central place.
To reach the Manage Your Compliance Dashboard, open the top menu by selecting the button with three
horizontal lines in the top left corner of the Seller Central home page.
Under Performance, select Account Health.
Once you're on the Account Health Dashboard, scroll to the bottom of the page to find a Manage Your
Compliance card.
From here, you can navigate to the Manage Your Compliance Dashboard.
This dashboard will show you at a glance any products that require documentation.
The dashboard shows not only each product's name but also their Amazon Standard Identification Numbers
or ASINs as well as their Stock Keeping Unit Numbers or SKUs.
You can see the specific documents or information that are required and the date by which they must
be provided.
You can also see the approval status for any documentation or information you've submitted.
You may be required to provide compliance documents or information if you intend to sell a product
that's subject to restrictions in your region's store.
The specific class of documents or information you need to upload is displayed on the dashboard.
To submit them, select the Add Appeal Compliance button to go to the Add Compliance page.
For each category of document that's been requested, you can drag and drop a file to upload or browse
your hard drive to find and select a file.
If you need more information about a request, hover over the question mark next to the name of the
request type.
Remember that files must be less than 25 megabytes and can only be submitted in a supported format
as indicated on the submission page.
If the files you submitted aren't supported, you'll get an error and will need to upload a new file.
If you feel that you need to explain any of your documents further, you can provide that information
in additional comments.
If you believe the request was made in error, you can appeal.
To do so, select Appeal Request above the area for submitting documents.
When you appeal, you must provide a reason, select the Appeal Reason from the drop-down list.
Again, you can explain your reason for the appeal in more detail in the additional comments field.
Once you've provided the documents you need, select Submit.
You can see the status of any of your compliance submissions or appeal requests from the Manage
Your Compliance dashboard.
If you select any item, you'll see an overview of the current status.
Remember that customer safety is everyone's responsibility.
By working together to document your product's compliance with policies and regulations,
we can help customers trust that products they purchase in the Amazon store are of the highest quality
and safe to use.
While different types of products may have different requirements, the Manage Your Compliance dashboard
will help you organize and monitor all compliance requests for your offers.
Whenever you need to check this dashboard, select Account Health under the Performance menu and
then select the card for Manage Your Compliance.
And if you need information about specific product types, check the Product Compliance Documentation
Help page on Seller Central for information about the types of documentation we request.
To watch this video again, search for Manage Your Compliance Dashboard on Seller University or bookmark
the page you're on right now for future reference.
This concludes our training on the Manage Your Compliance dashboard.
Thank you and happy selling in the Amazon store.